DONGJAE LEE

dongjae.lee@sf.snu.ac.kr • dongjaelee1.github.io • github.com/dongjaelee1

SUMMARY

I am currently a research assistant at Software Foundations Lab, Seoul National University. My current research interests include verifying realistic systems, concurrency, and security. I have research experience with the Coq proof assistant, compiler verification, concurrent program verification, and security.

EDUCATION

M.S., Computer Science and Engineering

02.2024

Seoul National University, Seoul, South Korea

B.S., Physics, Computer Science and Engineering (Double Major)

08.2021

Seoul National University, Seoul, South Korea

EXPERIENCE

Software Foundations Lab, Seoul National University

03.2024 - Current

Research Assistant: Seoul, South Korea

Max Planck Institute for Security and Privacy

03.2023 - 08.2023

Research Intern: Bochum, Germany

- · Advised by Cătălin Hrițcu
- Worked on secure compilation

Software Foundations Lab, Seoul National University

09.2020 - 08.2021

Research Intern: Seoul, South Korea

- · Advised by Chung-Kil Hur
- Worked on Conditional Contextual Refinement

ROK Army (Mandatory Military Service)

01.2019 - 08.2020

Sergeant: South Korea

Integrated Quantum Systems Lab, Seoul National University

04.2017 - 08.2017

Research Intern: Seoul, South Korea

- · Advised by Dohun Kim
- Worked on NV center qubits, programming and developing devices for experiments

PUBLICATIONS

SECOMP: Formally Secure Compilation of Compartmentalized C Programs

Jérémy Thibault, Roberto Blanco, **Dongjae Lee**, Sven Argo, Arthur Azevedo de Amorim, Aïna Linn Georges, Cătălin Hritcu, Andrew Tolmach.

Draft (https://arxiv.org/abs/2401.16277)

Stuttering for Free

Minki Cho*, Youngju Song*, **Dongjea Lee**, Lennard Gäher, Derek Dreyer.

International Conference on Object-Oriented Programming, Systems, Languages, and Applications (OOPSLA 2023)

Fair Operational Semantics

Dongjae Lee*, Minki Cho*, Jinwoo Kim, Soonwon Moon, Youngju Song, Chung-Kil Hur.

Conference on Programming Language Design and Implementation (PLDI 2023)

Conditional Contextual Refinement

Youngju Song, Minki Cho, **Dongjae Lee**, Chung-Kil Hur, Michael Sammler, Derek Dreyer.

Symposium on Principles of Programming Languages (POPL 2023)

^{*}equal contribution

Sequential Reasoning for Optimizing Compilers under Weak Memory Concurrency

Minki Cho*, Sung-Hwan Lee*, **Dongjae Lee**, Chung-Kil Hur, Ori Lahav.

Conference on Programming Language Design and Implementation (PLDI 2022)

HONORS AND AWARDS

ACTIVITIES

Master's Thesis Award	02.2024
Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Seoul National University: Seoul, South Korea	
TALKS	
Fair Operational Semantics PLDI 2023: Orlando, Florida, United States	06.2023
Overview of Fair Operational Semantics (as a part of introducing Software Foundations Lab) SIGPL Winter School 2023 (The Korean Institute of Information Scientists and Engineers): Seou	02.2023 II, South Korea
TEACHING	
TEACHING	
(TA) Topics in Programming Languages (Logic in computer science) by Makoto Tatsuta: Seoul National University, Graduate level course	09.2023 - 12.2023
(TA) Topics in Programming Languages (Logic in computer science)	09.2023 - 12.2023 09.2022 - 12.2022

Developing a Coq tutorial for refinement-based verification: https://github.com/mori1116/refinement-tutorial